Torbjorn ready to Vark
ahna they all thought you for dead
well I had to come back I was worried
you'd get bored not being able to stick
your nose in my business
I hate working Vitesse talking tin cans
hey stop following me around shoo
Bastien I bet you haven't had a systems
check in years who knows what kind of
weird behaviors you picked up
what do you think of my armor not bad
not bad I'm glad you let me add a little
something to it
your armor seems to be working well I
guess you were right about the core
integration design I knew you would come
around
any chance you'd let me peek under the
hood of your Mick
retirement suits you and I think a
hammer upside your face but suit you
machree
happen to your arm always admired yours
figured I'd get one of my own
I was wondering if I could take a look
at your little robot
I suppose so just keep the hammer to
yourself
I've been having the worst headaches
I've always said you should get your
head examined
hmm table YUM I miss Ingrid's epic pie
at the holidays he just so happens he
has some saved for you
Toby and Lindholm you are responsible in
part for my creation why does that feel
like an accusation
I consider Reinhart to be the model upon
which I have based my own behaviors but
a terrifying thought
hater bein check out my new suit mark
six state-of-the-art job Church
concussion rockets yes it's looking
pretty good
you know furry huh I could take a look
at fixing up your suit if you'd like and
mess it up with a bunch of scrap metal
bolted on the side no thanks I like it
the way it is
you always did take good care of my
armor just try to keep it in one piece
for once
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down yeah and I
sometimes wonder if your height is why
you're always in such a bad mood
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down huh
could you say that again sometimes it's
hard to hear you all the way down there
Reinhart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks Lou it
shows these kids how it's done
Rinehart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks agreed let
the best man win
how's Brigitta doing keeping everything
in working order a night could not ask
for more from his choir
Reinhardt you'd better not be filling my
daughter's head with stories huh she
hardly listens to her anyways
you know Torian you would make an
excellent Santa Claus oh maybe this here
you can be the elf I think Ingrid's been
working on something
there's something on your dress
no there isn't
armor how positively medieval yeah
everyone's a critic
armor how positively medieval
no one asked for your opinion
armor how positively medieval last I
checked I didn't ask for your opinion
I am impressed I would not think such
crude creations actually function why
thank you I must admit I'm surprised Hey
Princeton are you still using that silly
feather duster of a gun why don't you
come over here and ask that again
the suffering of my people arrests
heavily upon your shoulders Thorburn
believe me I don't need reminding
I hear that you have taken in an omni
table yarn I don't want to talk about it
don't tell your mother about this
Papa knows best
ha teach you that
you need more seasoning
who still have a lot to learn
I told you the size of the hammers not
important
hahahahaha see size doesn't matter
back to the strap heap
back to the slag heaps
good shot for a machine
that's my daughter
that's the Lindhome way
that makes me a proud papa